downloadhelper.net 2001-12-05

# Privacy Policy

####  Privacy Policy

We at Aladdin Systems, Inc. recognize your right to confidentiality and are committed to protecting your privacy. Protecting your privacy is important to us; the information contained herein strives to help you understand just how much personal information is (and is not) collected on our web site and how it is used.

**Automatic Information Collection**  
When navigating our web site, personal information about you is not collected automatically. On the StuffIt Expander and DropStuff pages of our site of our website, we do log the IP address of your computer to help us validate the opt-in to our mailing list. This does not disclose any personal information about you.

**About Cookies**  
As is the case with many web sites, certain portions of Aladdin's web site may utilize a common technology known as "cookies" to collect and/or store information about you. A cookie is small amount of data that is transferred to your browser by a Web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. A cookie cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses.

Our online store, which is powered by Digital River, utilizes cookies to store information such as your name and address. (IMPORTANT: information is only taken from what you have typed into the online form and not your hard drive.)

The cookie file is important because it allows Digital River to make sure that you are who you say you are when you come back into their system and it also prevents anyone from using your information to place orders. It is also convenient because when you come back to the online store the Digital River system will recognize you and enter in your name and address for you into the order form when you place a new order. 

These files in no way allow us to access your hard drive at anytime; it only allows your system to tell us that you have previously visited our site.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. Our system is completely cookie dependent and you must receive ALL cookies to order from our online store.

**Aladdin Software sending information via the Internet**  
Some of our software products have been equipped with a version checking feature. Upon launching the software application, the version of the application you are running is captured and sent to our webserver. It is compared to the most current shipping version and if there is an update available the software will notify you of how to obtain it. There is no personal information sent to our server, only information from the software application itself.

**E-mail Addresses and Their Usage**  
Aladdin asks that you enter your e-mail address on our download pages before downloading software. You always have the option to not provide your e-mail address; it is not a requirement to download our software. Aladdin does not sell, trade or rent your email address to others. We ask for your e-mail address so that we may contact you to inform you of updates, special offers, or other software that we think would be of interest to you, including software or products from companies other than Aladdin. Any offer you may receive via email will always come from Aladdin, not the sponsoring third party. We know that the members of our e-mail list are very sensitive to receiving spam, or unsolicited email; hence we are very careful about what we send out and to whom.

When you participate in a contest, promotion or survey, we may ask for your name, address, e-mail address or other information.

At any time, you may choose to not be included in e-mail messages from Aladdin by visiting our Mailing List Page and unsubscribing your email address.

**Security of Information**  
When you place an order for a product, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all the information you input before it is sent to us.

**Third Party Information**  
Aladdin Systems, Inc works with a third party that serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Flycast manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.engage.com/privacy/>.
